<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.omg.sysml.feature"
      label="SysML v2 Feature"
      version="0.1.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="SysML v2 Submission Team">

   <description url="http://www.example.com/description">
      UI plugins for the SysML v2 pilot implementation of editors for the textual notation for the Kernel Model Language (KerML) and the Systems Modeling Language (SysML).
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright (c) 2019 Model Drive Solutions, Inc.
Copyright (c) 2019 California Institute of Technology (Jet Propulsion Laboratory)
Copyright (c) 2019 IncQuery Labs Ltd.
Copyright (c) 2019 Itemis
   </copyright>

   <license url="">
      Copyright (c) 2019 Model Drive Solutions, Inc.
Copyright (c) 2019 California Institute of Technology (Jet Propulsion Laboratory)
Copyright (c) 2019 IncQuery Labs Ltd.
Copyright (c) 2019 Itemis

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &quot;Software&quot;), to use and redistribute the Software and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the conditions that the above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies of the Software. No permission is granted to modify, merge, and/or sell copies of the Software, or to create derivative works based on the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="org.omg.sysml.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.omg.kerml.xtext.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.omg.sysml.xtext.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.omg.kerml.xtext.ide"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.omg.sysml.xtext"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.omg.sysml.xtext.ide"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.omg.sysml"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.omg.sysml.ide"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.omg.kerml.xtext"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
